And then the pants part is frozen.
Okay, the next step is to do this knotting part.
The knotting must be the part that everyone is more concerned about.
So let's take the clothes first.
Make a big shape of the clothes first.
Okay, for this big shape, we will use the T-shirt we brought in the software.
And then put it all together.
After you put it all together, remember to rearrange the board.
Okay, after arranging it, we are going to make a baseball uniform.
Because everyone should be able to see it.
This part of my knotting should be able to feel that it is a bit like the effect of a baseball uniform.
Then let's put this baseball uniform on the model first.
After wearing it, let's do this knotting.
In fact, this knotting is more convenient than you think.
It's not that hard.
Okay, if you make a baseball uniform, you must catch this characteristic.
For example, its shoulders are very wide.
Is the indoor-outdoor effect picture high in the requirements of learning MD?
I don't think it's very high.
The indoor-outdoor effect picture is for indoor design, which is the sofa, right?
For these, you can take a look at the sofa study live broadcast we did before.
Because it doesn't have very high requirements for the board shape.
Okay, so we mentioned earlier that
the indoor-outdoor effect picture is very high in the requirements of learning MD.
But if you want to make this kind of wider clothes,
Oops, my head is stuck.
Wait a minute.
Oh, right, we are going to make the shoulders.
Because I was looking at the chat box and it said
is the indoor-outdoor effect picture high in the requirements of learning MD?
Because I know that if you make a sofa,
you will use MD to make a sofa bed.
Okay.
MD,
what configuration do you recommend is better?
For the laptop, the first one is the laptop itself.
Its performance in the same configuration is not as good as the table.
So there is a tendency to raise the table or raise the table.
The whole cost-effectiveness will also be a little higher.
Then if I recommend the configuration, I just want to remind everyone.
First of all, the AMD CPU,
when using AMD,
there will be a little lag.
Then,
so it's best to use Intel's CPU.
And for the graphics card,
buy an NVIDIA graphics card.
Of course, the newer the better.
If you are looking for a cost-effective one,
you can also buy a 2000 series.
Because the 40 series is about to come out,
or it has already come out.
The previous graphics card will definitely be cheaper.
Right?
Okay.
Just now we put this shoulder,
we have mentioned that if you want to make a relatively loose clothes,
then first of all,
you must definitely stretch the whole body,
that is to say.
Another point is to pay attention to the shoulder.
The point of the shoulder,
let's move it out.
Let it form an effect of falling shoulder.
Don't be the original,
the position of the shoulder.
Because if you think about it,
if you wear a relatively loose clothes,
then the shoulder line will basically fall out.
Okay.
After the shoulder falls out,
because of the point of our shoulder just now,
does it move out?
So as it is,
your sleeve here,
does it have to change with your shoulder?
So the point of the sleeve has to move down a little bit.
Do you understand?
So when you are changing clothes,
you must pay attention to your point,
you have to match it.
Understand?
Okay.
Then after we match the point of our sleeve,
just put this sleeve,
the highest point down a little bit.
Because your shoulder line has become longer,
your sleeve has to become shorter.
Understand?
Okay.
After it becomes shorter,
your whole curve
also has to become a little bit flatter.
Because our curve was like this before.
From this point,
bend over.
But from here,
it is a straight line.
So its curve is not so blurry.
Okay.
Without AMD,
it is impossible to use the line-based shredder to solidify.
Yes.
You can still use AMD's CPU.
It's just that sometimes,
there will be some accidental lags.
This is not just a problem with our software.
In fact,
sometimes,
with some other software,
with AMD's CPU,
there may also be this problem.
And when we test it backstage,
in fact,
we rarely encounter these lags.
There are more feedback from users.
We also made a hand test before,
how to try to optimize your AMD CPU
to run Marvelous Designer more smoothly.
But if you are talking about GPU,
there is no way.
Because our software
uses some acceleration functions of NVIDIA.
So we don't support using this problem.
Yes.
This motherboard problem,
in fact,
we have considered.
Because when we tested the AMD CPU in the Korean headquarters,
there was no problem.
So...
Just...
Yes.
OK.
Let's put this curve line...
Don't send it.
I saw you posted a lot of comments.
Thank you.
OK.
After we modify its curve line,
we can start preparing for other adjustments.
OK.
As we said just now,
I will repeat it again.
Adjust the shoulder here.
And the curve line
should not be so obvious.
Like this kind of loose clothes,
or those clothes that men are more rough,
it generally doesn't have this kind of obvious curve line.
Its direction is generally relatively simple,
relatively straight.
Then we lengthen the sleeves a little longer.
Yes.
Marvelous Designer is a Korean software.
OK.
Then we adjust its sleeves again.
Of course,
if you want to make a knot,
your sleeves...
My suggestion is to make it a little longer.
It's more convenient to make a knot like this.
But don't make it too long.
We will use a new fabric for the sleeves here.
OK.
In order to arrange it quickly,
we sew it directly,
then select the sleeve,
the sleeve opening,
and then add it to the side.
When adding to the side,
sometimes it will turn inside.
Then here we just need to select it again,
add it to the side,
and it will automatically turn out.
Understand?
This is also to arrange it quickly.
Of course,
you can also arrange it directly with the arrangement point.
OK.
Then we freeze the sleeves,
and then lengthen the sleeves a little longer.
OK.
Then we adjust the width of the sleeve,
the width of the sleeve connection.
OK.
In fact,
I didn't think about what tool to use for my knot here.
Is it to use this dress directly?
Or is it to add another plate to it?
So when I made it here,
I started with it as an ordinary baseball uniform as a reference to modify it.
Then it is also to increase some width.
Then you must remember that when you increase the width of the sleeve,
your shoulder line will follow your shoulder line.
It will change with your shoulder width.
After this change,
everyone must remember to think about which line to sew with this line.
With this line of sewing,
should we also adjust it at the same time?
These are all places to remember to think about and pay attention to.
Then we sew the inner line of the bottom white again.
After sewing,
put this bottom white plate in a little bit.
Let it have the effect of making a waist.
Then the bottom plate is a little bit narrow.
Let's make it a little wider.
In fact,
the point of knotting is to learn to use a fixed needle
and use some special physical properties,
such as friction.
Then let's make a collar.
Although you can't see the collar at the end,
let's briefly introduce it to you.
How to make a collar like this.
A collar like a baseball bat.
First, we draw a rectangular plate.
Then put this rectangular plate on the side.
After that,
we open the simulation by pressing the control key.
Here, pay attention to my operation.
Here in the middle of my back.
In the middle of our back,
sometimes you can sew it first.
After sewing,
you can adjust it.
The model that is inserted from the outside
will definitely become a triangle.
In order to simulate it more quickly.
So,
at present,
it cannot maintain the original
grid layout.
At this point,
I can mention a function development requirement later.
That is to maintain the original face.
But,
how to say?
This may not be so well developed
or the feedback of the people,
but not so much.
Now, we can see that it is a collar.
But, what we are going to do at the end
is to make a collar that is
attached to the neck of the baseball bat.
So, what we are going to do next
is to modify this collar
to make it meet the effect we want.
The overall particle diameter should be reduced first.
This is also
the usual operation.
OK.
Here we have an operation.
You can see that
I will drag a point of the collar
and press it down.
When I drag the point of the collar
and pull it down,
it actually starts to fit the neck.
So, if we put this point,
which is the original collar,
this point is outside.
Now, we move this point
back here.
Will this collar
become
more fit to the neck?
Next,
we will repeat some operations.
For example,
here,
when I click this point
and drag it down,
will this collar
be more fit to the neck?
So, what we are going to do
is to adjust this point
to here.
In the middle,
we add a straight point
or we can adjust it manually
and draw some curves.
All of them are fine.
After drawing,
here,
choose to cut.
Then, delete the excess part.
OK.
After deleting it,
extend this line again.
Let's simulate it again.
OK.
Here,
actually,
there are some shapes
that fit the neck.
So, what we are going to do
is to repeat the previous operation.
For example,
when I drag the plate,
pull this collar
and look at it.
After clicking it,
there is a blue point here.
Then,
quickly go to the 2D window
and find its corresponding position.
Then,
refer to that position
to adjust the plate.
For example,
here, we bring this point
up a little bit more.
Will this collar
be more fit to the neck now?
In fact,
we delete this point
and directly make a round corner here.
Then, sew it.
It is actually
the collar we want
that fits the neck.
After that,
because of the corner in the middle,
the corner just now
is not very smooth.
Here,
there is a protruding point.
So, when we observe
the simulation effect
in the 3D window,
there is also a corner here.
There is also a corner here.
So, we
round this corner here.
Round it with the round curve tool.
OK.
Thank you.
Thank you, Mr. Yu.
OK.
Now,
the position of the collar
and the clothes
is basically adjusted.
Now,
what we need to do
is to make it
a round
and a curve
collar.
In this way,
we can just
use the round curve tool
to pull out
the curve here.
OK.
Finally,
adjust the seam line.
OK.
You can see
that after we adjust it a little bit,
the collar
actually becomes
the effect we want.
So, when you are adjusting,
you can try to drag the panel
in the 3D space
to see if,
for example,
if we move this point
here,
will it make the collar
become the effect
we want?
If you move one point
to another point,
the overall curve
is smooth,
that means
the middle part
has to be dug out.
Understand?
Because in this way,
you can turn the seam line
to this point.
Let it
become a line.
So, these operations
are something that
you can try
in the process
that you usually do.
OK.
Then,
because this collar
is not very close to the neck,
so I am doing
some basic operations now.
For example,
adjust its length
and
position like this.
But the overall,
because,
because if you look directly
at a panel,
or if you draw a panel
manually,
you don't know
how its structure
is distributed.
For example,
where is the straight line
and where is the curve line?
Then, you can
sew a rectangle
directly on it,
and then
make some changes.
OK.
After that,
I think that
this dress,
if it is sewn
here in the front,
then
I can't see
the top of
the seat, right?
So,
in the end,
I think that
I should
use this dress
to tie the knot.
Then, I think
where should I
tie the knot?
Should I
tie it on the shoulder
or on the waist?
Then,
I think about it,
and I refer to
my friends.
They are
those girls
who are
Y2K.
What kind of clothes
do they wear?
Then, I imagine
that they usually
tie this dress
on the waist.
So,
we can start
to tie the knot.
Finally,
it's time to tie the knot.
First of all,
let's reduce
the diameter
to 10.
OK.
Here,
I'm dragging the shawl
to make sure
that the
sleeve
won't
be
blocked.
Because
later,
we will
drag the sleeve
to tie the knot.
But,
later,
I found that
no matter what,
it will be blocked.
Haha.
OK.
Here,
I have
increased
its
length,
so that
the sleeve
will be
a little bit
tighter.
This is also
my personal
adjustment
to this
shape.
It's because
I think that
the shawl
just now
looks too
soft.
And,
it has
a good
elasticity.
I hope
it has
some support.
And,
its shawl
is relatively
irregular
and hard.
So,
I will
increase
its
elastic
strength
a little bit.
Oh,
it's not
QK.
It's
style
Y2K.
Wait a minute.
I will
type it
in the
chat.
It's a little bit
like
more
vintage.
And,
it feels
like
around
2000,
millennium.
It's a little bit
better.
OK.
Then,
I will
decrease
the
elastic
strength
a little bit.
This way,
it can
make its
shawl
thinner
and more
obvious.
I want to
imitate the
silk texture.
Because,
many silk
clothes
are not
easy to
stretch.
And,
its shawl
is very
thin.
It looks
a little bit
tight on the
body.
In fact,
when your
physical properties,
for example,
you have
a concept
about the
strength of
the
silk,
and the
strength of the
shawl,
you will
adjust it
manually.
Just like me,
I don't
adjust it
with the
shawl.
OK.
Here,
we draw
the inner
line.
Then,
when you
copy and paste,
press the
right button
to paste
a lot of
roots at the
same time.
Then,
ctrl c,
ctrl r,
create a
symmetrical one.
Let's do
the position of
the
zero
grid.
Here,
we draw
the inner
line,
then we
paste it.
So,
when we
paste the
inner
line,
it will
be
stuck.
This kind of
stuck
can
affect
the
effect of
our
paste.
So,
we need
to adjust
the curve.
That is,
we can't
do the
double
So now we can't set the conflict thickness of the board directly to 1.
Because the conflict thickness of the board is the air thickness around the board.
When your board is cutting, the air in the middle will be squeezed very, very little, and then very close, very close.
So the board is almost stuck between the board and the board.
At this time, if you want to insert a layer of the board into the board, it will definitely be unstable, it will definitely conflict.
Understand? So here we want to increase its conflict thickness first.
When cutting, let it have enough space in the middle, and then we can add a layer in the middle.
So let's increase its air thickness first.
Let it have a reserved position in the middle.
Understand?
After cutting, we add two fixed pins on both sides.
Okay.
If you understand, please respond to me.
Otherwise, I will be very worried here, worried that you don't understand.
And if you don't understand, you can ask directly.
I will answer you, okay?
Okay.
So about the conflict thickness just now.
We need to increase the conflict thickness in advance.
Do you understand this point?
Okay.
Okay, so now we add the fixed pins on both sides.
Of course, if you move this board directly through the fixed pins, it is more inconvenient.
How to take it off is to pull out the entire jacket directly in the 3D space.
Pull it out with the positioning ball.
After pulling it out, add two fixed pins on both sides to fix the sleeves.
Now you can adjust it directly.
Ah, it doesn't matter that we haven't reached the part of the knot yet.
Simply put, this piece of clothing, we are going to make it into a double-layer clothing later.
If you go directly to the double-layer situation, there will be a loop.
If you go directly to the double-layer situation, the knot will affect you and it may not be stable.
When we tie the knot, because the board will be twisted, they will not be stable.
So our double-layer structure is usually after the knot is finished,
the board is directly used with the clove layer and then add a layer inside.
After adding a layer inside, the board in the middle will have a conflict.
Because it itself has a conflict thickness.
So we use the conflict thickness to reserve some space for it to come out.
Because the conflict thickness is the thickness of the air.
It's like two boards.
We leave a little more space in the middle for it.
After that, we add the board in.
Then reduce the conflict thickness of the new board and the original board.
So we have enough space to add a layer in the middle.
So we need to reverse the operation first.
Add the conflict thickness first.
So reserve some space.
After that, we are in the clove layer.
That's it.
Then adjust it with the fixing pin.
Here we use the fixing pin to support the point here in the back.
Otherwise, it will move during the adjustment process.
So we must first find a point.
Then add a fixing pin to stop the clothes from moving.
For example, when I wrap it around my waist now,
when I turn on the simulation,
to drag the fixing pin, it can be wrapped around my waist.
After that, I think that,
the texture of the body may seem a little stiff when it is wrapped around my waist.
I need it to be more in line with the curve of the waist.
It needs to be more vertical.
It needs to be more flexible.
So I reduce the strength of the clove and the tension of the toe line a little bit.
You can see the point in the back.
After I adjust it,
for example, I have already crossed the two sleeves in the front.
Just now, while I was modeling,
I went to drag the fixing pin to make the cross.
After it can be fixed here,
I may delete the fixing pin.
In the process of modeling,
press the mouse button,
or in the process of you not modeling,
as long as this version is not frozen,
press the W key on the keyboard,
and then click the mouse button on the left,
you can instantly create a fixing pin on a grid point.
When we are knotting,
pay attention to create more fixing pins.
Because if you knot directly,
the board will have conflicts.
You are not like in real life,
you can just knot directly.
So in the process of modeling,
you need to use the fixing pin first,
make the space in the middle for it,
and then put the position you want to knot into it.
So here,
we add some fixing pins,
and then the length of the sleeve,
I think it is a little short,
so we will modify the length of the sleeve in the middle.
You see,
like this kind of modification,
the length of the sleeve,
if your board is two layers,
then its grid will inevitably increase with your board,
and there will be some conflicts.
These may affect the stability of the board.
So we still remind you again,
we do a layer first,
and then come out in the Cologne layer.
OK,
here you can see I have an operation,
that is, when I was modeling,
I opened this board, right?
After I opened it,
I added a fixing pin,
so that its intersection point is fixed by me.
Wait a minute,
I just need to put this sleeve
into this hollow place,
that's it.
Then the particle diameter is also reduced,
don't make it unstable,
and then drag it by hand,
because I'm a little forced,
I have to look at it from the back,
it's right,
that's it.
OK,
then the sleeve here,
give it a new fabric,
this fabric,
we individually increase its friction coefficient,
everyone will definitely be in the process of simulation,
especially in the process of knotting,
you will find that your knotting is often scattered,
right?
That's because there is its own friction coefficient
between the fabric and the fabric.
The default friction coefficient is relatively small,
this knot,
when you use it more,
it will slide together,
slide to the end,
it will be scattered,
but if you increase the friction coefficient,
then there will be friction between the fabric and the fabric,
to prevent relative sliding,
it can also prevent the last part of the board from being scattered,
the knotting position is scattered,
so,
because we want to knot with the sleeve,
so the sleeve here,
we give it a relatively high friction coefficient,
because other parts,
for example,
like our back,
if your friction coefficient is relatively high,
this board is,
it may not have such a natural,
smooth effect,
because it has friction,
the friction effect,
it can be operated by the GPU,
but GPU simulation,
although it is fast,
but it is not as high as the CPU operation,
so I personally prefer to use the CPU to calculate,
especially when doing multi-layer structure,
the CPU is much better than the GPU,
OK,
the graphics card,
yes,
the graphics card is not very high,
and then you can see that I am in the process of simulation,
I will observe this hollow part in real time,
we have to be more detailed here,
because I hope everyone can focus a little bit,
OK,
we have to give it a hollow place in the middle here,
after the hollow place is reserved,
add some fixing needles to it,
and then a little bit,
because if you wear it now,
it will be unstable if the board and the board are tight,
so we need to use the fixing needle first,
to reserve this hollow part first,
and then a little bit,
you see,
here,
is it that we just blocked the fabric,
so we manually take the fabric out a little bit,
add a fixing needle to it,
fix it,
now we can visually see this fabric,
after that,
we will move on to the fixing needle,
I am more experienced in knotting,
so I wear it faster,
so when you make this dress yourself,
you can be patient and come slowly,
do you understand?
OK,
then we will delete the excess fixing needles,
and then because we just increased the friction rate,
so it is now moving together,
the sliding is relatively slow,
it can follow us,
delete the fixing needles in the middle,
it will slowly solve it by itself,
and then,
drag it to the right position,
yes, yes, yes,
to add the fixing needle,
the shortcut is to click on the W button,
the official MD course is taught by me,
but,
now,
because the price has been adjusted to the normal price,
so,
yes,
because I saw an ID,
I really can't forget it,
that ID is too noticeable,
I don't know if it was done by my colleague,
press the left mouse button,
right,
yes, yes,
I press the left mouse button,
press W,
and left mouse button,
exactly,
yes, yes,
yes,
then you can see,
we delete all the fixing needles in the middle,
because we are pulling the sleeves directly,
and the friction rate is relatively high,
so,
no, no,
So it will automatically pull it up like this
I think you guys need to focus a little bit
Did you see what Hana was holding in her hand?
It's because I uploaded this live stream
So when I was making this outfit
I was going to make her a big scissor
But...
But in the end, I think the scissor and Hana's style are a little bit different
So I changed it to a softer weapon
Right
If you tie it here
This part is actually almost over
So
If you want to remember one thing
Just use this conflict thickness to preserve some of the air thickness
This will help us to insert more pieces afterwards
And then tap W to add a fixed needle
After adding the fixed needle
We can go and put that knot position
First, let go of its hollow part
After that, through the improvement of friction coefficient, we can also change the area of the knot.
to make it easier for the tiles to fall apart
It's because they are tied, so it's not easy to fall apart
And then the tiles can also be slowly
through slower and more stable simulation
to achieve the effect we want
I'm live right now
Okay, after that, did you see that
our collision thickness was 5 before
Now let's change its collision thickness to 3
Pay attention to it
The collision thickness was originally 5, and now it's changed to 3 or 2
After changing, is the air thickness around us thinner now?
This means we can
Don't do the simulation at this time
If you open it, it will
It will recalculate your collision thickness again
And then here we choose the interior of the column
After doing the interior of the column
Remember
We are now
After using the interior of the column
Remember to look at the collision thickness of this column
You can see that our collision thickness is actually set to 3
That is to say, our original collision thickness is 5, right?
So if we now reduce the collision thickness to half
Why change 3
It's because if you use the original collision thickness of 5
Then your air is going to squeeze the tiles again
Let me draw a picture
Draw a picture
For example, this tile
Wait a minute, I'll use the mouse to draw
For example, our original tile is like this, right?
And then its
And then the other tile is like this
And then when we hit the knot
These two tiles are very close
And then this
The air thickness is 5
The top is 5, the bottom is 5
So added together is 10
Right?
OK
Then after we hit the knot
Because we want to pierce it in the middle
Then here is also a pierce
So if this layer
It is this layer
Its air thickness is also 5
Then here is 4 5
It's a total of 20
But when we tie the knot
This knot is like this
Like this
Then you were 10
Now suddenly give it 20
Then this knot starts
You have to draw it like this
Then it starts to shake and shake
Not stable
Although I drew it a little abstract
But you can understand
So when we tie the knot
After this
We are going to put it
Just reduce its collision thickness to half
For example, 2.5
I gave it 3 because I was more experienced
3 or 2.5 are OK
In this way
After we put the four layers together
It's the same as the previous
The overall air thickness is the same
So that this knot will not be dispersed
Understand?
OK
After that, in this process
We are not open to simulation
Now we have done all these air thicknesses in the column
This collision thickness has been reduced
After reducing
We can start to simulate
Of course, this layer
I'm not too relieved
I still reduced its collision thickness a little
Then you open the simulation
It will be a little unstable
Look at me here
Reduce the collision thickness
It's a little unstable
If we still use it
Is the previous air thickness
Is it going to be particularly unstable?
So we need to reserve the air thickness
Then use the dragon layer
Now this dress will be
It's already a good knot
Then there is a double-layer structure
And when everyone is knotting
Be sure to pay attention
When you go to drag
During the process of dragging the fixed needle
Be sure to observe your board at all times
Is there any deformation
Let's talk about the deformation
What kind of problem is it?
For example, when we are knotting
This is a board
it is good
When we are pulling
There is no problem like this
But if you pull it very long
Because in Marvelous Designer
It is not in a state of recognition
But at this time
In fact, the whole board is very unstable
Its overall strength is very strong
In this case
It is difficult to maintain the form of knotting
It
Even if you put
No matter how high the friction coefficient adjustment
It will be unstable
So when you are pulling
You have to make sure
Pay attention to observe your board
Is there any serious stretching deformation
How to observe
You go to observe
The board connected to it
Or with it
Related to this fabric position
When you are pulling
Look
Is it down here
There is a strange triangle
Or some curve
It means that it is now
The stretching deformation is serious
At this time
We either make up for its length
Make it a little longer
In this case
It is also easy to adjust the single-layer structure
We talked about this before
Otherwise
You just set this fixing pin a little closer
Just don't let it pull so long
Understand
This is why I still emphasize
That is to say
I think you should play single layer first
Then double layer in the column
It's convenient to play like this
Because this is also more convenient to modify
Understand
OK
Finally, let's adjust it a little bit
Where to adjust the friction between the boards
After selecting the physical properties of the selected fabric
At the bottom of the property editor
There is a friction value
Here
At the bottom
There is a friction value at the bottom
You can increase it
OK
Then reduce the strength of the particle
And adjust some other things
That's it
I fixed it for him at the end
It's fixed temporarily with a fake sewing needle
Good at the time of molding
You have to observe at all times
See if there is such a small
Unstable place
If there is
Handle it manually
Good
Then we will
Be careful when you take off this fixing needle
Of course, here
I will speed up some processes
I just took it off with a fixing needle
Drag it to the side
Finally, use a fake sewing needle to fix it
Fixed on the model
So that when we change the action
It won't fall off
The fake sewing needle is to put two points
Fixed temporarily
Because the fixing needle is fixed in the 3D window
And the fake sewing needle is to sew the two points together
So you see
It won't fall off in the process of our overall simulation
Because I just fixed these two points
On the board
OK
Here, after we simulated
The creases of the pants here are a little dissipated
Take a look again
Because I have a habit
Is that I will freeze the board when I sit
But in fact
Between the board and the board
It must still affect each other
So when I sit in the middle
I will unfreeze it all
And then simulate it together
Unless it's some special structures
For example, like a sofa
Its inner layer must always be frozen
And it's invisible
Otherwise
Remember to unfreeze it at any time after you freeze it
And then simulate it collectively
Because I'm in the process of simulation
In fact, you can see
After a while of social simulation
The creases of the pants are dissipated
So let's use the model to fix it
So that the creases of the pants
Will not dissipate themselves
You can see that after I simulated
It doesn't have any of these
Unstable or something
Or the creases will dissipate
There is no problem
This is all due to our previous
Better operating habits
Give yourself a hand
Because we just
Increased the friction of the fabric
Then the two sides are also fixed with a sewing needle
Now the pants are also shaped
Let its creases not dissipate